giancarlonabormagdaleno@gmail.com | 09227435159 | 09226404408 171-0-1 22nd Avenue, East Rembo, Makati City, Philippines



Summary

Graduated of Bachelor of Science in Computer Science in Pamantasan ng Lungsod ng Pasig with a 02-year experience with the information technology (I.T) industry and 05 months of experience with a BPO company, total of 02 year and 05 months of overall experience who possesses a combination of skills, who can deliver an exceptional work, passionate, work-driven and can work well with other people and adjust/adapt to new environment/cultures.

Technical Skills

Development: PHP, VB.NET, Android Development (Java),

Database: MySQL, MS SQL Server, MS ACCESS, Google's

Firestore/Firebase

Scripting: jQuery, JavaScript
Markup Language: HTML, HTML5
Design Skills: CSS/CSS3, Bootstrap

Software Applications

And IDEs: Visual studio code, Visual Studio, Android Studio, Notepad ++,

Sublime Text, Photoshop, NetBeans, XAMPP, Jira

Version Control: GIT/GitHub

OS: Linux (Ubuntu), Windows 7, 8.1, 10

Portfolio

giancarlonabormagdaleno@gmail.com | 09227435159 | 09226404408 171-0-1 22nd Avenue, East Rembo, Makati City, Philippines



SKILLS QUALIFICATION			
SKILLS	YEARS OF EXPERIENCE	PROFICIENCY 01-05 (05 being the highest)	LAST YEAR USED (Last year you have used the skill you have indicated)
JavaScript	01 Year, 03 Months	03.70	2021
HTML	00 Year, 09 Months	03.70	2021
CSS	00 Year, 09 Months	03.60	2021
Android Development	00 Year, 08 Months	03.20	2020
Jira	01 Year, 04 Months	03.10	2021
Angular (Not AngularJS)	00 Year, 05 Months	03.00	2021
PHP	00 Year, 04 Months	03.00	2019
VB.NET	00 Year, 02 Months	03.00	2018
Git/GitHub	01 Year, 07 Months	02.60	2021
MySQL Database	00 Year, 02 Months	02.25	2019
Google Firebase/Firestore Database	00 Year, 02 Months	02.25	2019
MS SQL Server Database	00 Year, 02 Months	02.25	2018
Linux (Ubuntu) Operating System	01 Year, 00 Month	02.10	2020
jQuery	01 Year, 03 Months	01.90	2021
AJAX	01 Year, 03 Months	01.90	2021
Azure DevOps	00 Year, 05 Months	01.50	2021
Laravel	00 Year, 02 Months	01.00	2020
Bootstrap	00 Year, 02 Months	01.00	2018

Portfolio

giancarlonabormagdaleno@gmail.com | 09227435159 | 09226404408 171-0-1 22nd Avenue, East Rembo, Makati City, Philippines



Professional Experience

Accenture Philippines (Work from Home)

Application Development Analyst – Software Engineer (Front-End Web Developer [Angular])
May 31, 2021 – Present

- Chief Information Officer Quality and Risk
 - Worked with IDRA UI An Accenture's internal tool used to determine the quality and risk of a certain opportunity of a project.
 - Angular
 - Git
 - Azure DevOps
 - AWS (Lambda)

Joinpiggy (AIC Burgundy Empire Tower [Burgundy Empire Tower Asia Development Bank Avenue Corner Garnet Road, Ortigas Center, Quezon City, 1655 Metro Manila]) **JavaScript Developer** (JS DEV / Front-End)

January 27, 2020 – May 20, 2021

- The company's browser extension enables users to automatically apply coupon codes upon checking out with an online merchant to save money and earn cash back rewards.
- As a JavaScript Front-End Developer, we are working closely and only with the extension's modal, we do not work with the design or front-end (full stack devs) as they have a separate developer assigned for that.
- We ensure that the user have a smooth experience with applying coupon codes and earning cash back rewards.
- Peer to peer code reviews is done (GitHub) to ensure that the code is accurate and has less probability of having errors before letting the QA thoroughly test it before going into production.
- The following are used within the company: Visual Studio Code, Browser, Joinpiggy's browser extension, Windows/Linux (Ubuntu) Operating Systems, GitHub, Jira, JavaScript, and a little bit of jQuery and ajax

Nfinite IT Solutions (3 Calle Uno Bldg. Escoda St [First Road] cor. Naguilian Road, Quezon Hill) October 01, 2019 – January 27, 2020

PHP Developer (Homebased Project)

• A homebased project which lasted for about three months

Portfolio

giancarlonabormagdaleno@gmail.com | 09227435159 | 09226404408 171-0-1 22nd Avenue, East Rembo, Makati City, Philippines



- The developer agreed that I will be working only on my free time or when I was not working with Teleperformance Philippines at the time
- The work I helped with was the project relating with barangay system, specifically, registry of barangay inhabitants.
- Helped/Worked with some of the design, log-in page, also with the database using MySQL
- Used PHP, HTML, CSS and a little bit of JavaScript with this one

Teleperformance Philippines (*SM Aura Premier* [26th Street, Corner McKinley Pkwy, Taguig, 1630 Metro Manila])

Caption Agent/Captioning Agent/Captioning Assistant September 17, 2019 – January 25, 2020

- Helping the deaf and/or hard of hearing person with communicating to other people on the line by repeating everything and whatever the people on the other line says
- Used a software called 'dragon' which will then translate whatever you say into a text or a string
- The converted texts or strings will be sent over to the deaf/hard of hearing's special phone with a screen on it has and then they will just read whatever is on there
- Worked with a nightshift/graveyard shift

Nityo Infotech (*Lazada Express* [Sortation Site], Tanyag, Taguig) IT Support (A 3-week contract for their sale at that time) July 02, 2019 – July 24, 2019

- My role there as was to help their IT Support in fixing the hardware problems being encountered by the staffs/Lazada employees/Lazada workers, these includes, problems with printers (not printing, out of ink etc.), no internet connectivity, trouble shooting of the printers etc.
- Solving of problems are ticketing based using Jira

Bases Conversion and Development Authority (BCDA [2/F Bonifacio Technology Center, 31st Street corner 2nd Avenue, Bonifacio Global City, Taguig])
IT Helpdesk/Programmer (On-The-Job Training Program)
Jan 2019 to May 2019

• Helped with the company's programmer about their PSMES – Project Schedule Monitoring and Evaluation System by writing JavaScript codes in the script editor using Google Sheets Objective Looking for a challenging role to grow as a person. Utilize and expand my knowledge and skills as I socialize with other people especially with my co-workers.

Portfolio

giancarlonabormagdaleno@gmail.com | 09227435159 | 09226404408 171-0-1 22nd Avenue, East Rembo, Makati City, Philippines



• Also helped with their IT Support/Helpdesk – Doing things like troubleshooting and solving on the problems encountered by the employees like no internet connection, problems encountered with their printers, their own workstation PCs etc.

Educational Attainment

Pamantasan ng Lungsod ng Pasig, Kapasigan, Pasig Bachelor of Science in Computer Science College | 2015-2019

7th Ave, East Rembo, Makati City Tibagan High School High School | 2011-2015

Seminars Attended

2016: CGI (Creating the Grandiose Illusion)

2016: Ethical Hacking

2018: IT Security (Public Wi-Fi Security)

2019: Blockchain

Portfolio

giancarlonabormagdaleno@gmail.com | 09227435159 | 09226404408 171-0-1 22nd Avenue, East Rembo, Makati City, Philippines



Character References

Michael F. Isiguen Owner Nfinite IT Solutions (Contact): 09279013589

(Email): <u>isiguen.michael@gmail.com</u>

Alexander S. Mijares Information Technology Officer I Bases Conversion and Development Authority (BCDA)

(Contact): 09173064089 (Tel): 575-1745

(Email): asmijares@bcda.gov.ph

Noreen M. Arcangel, MIT Computer Science Dept. Head Pamantasan ng Lungsod ng Pasig (Contact): 09357049895

I hereby certify that the above information is true and correct to the best of my knowledge and belief.

GIAN CARLO N. MAGDALENO
Applicant

Portfolio